[WIND HOWLING]
(Howard:)- Damn it.
- What?
(Leonard:)We're out of ice.
All right, we begin initial assembly and
deployment of the testing equipment...
(Sheldon:)...starting tomorrow at 0700 hours,
but until then, you are all off duty.
(Sheldon:)I suggest you keep the shenanigans
to a minimum...
(Sheldon:)...as medical help is 18 hours away
by dogsled.
- What are you working on?
- Crossbow.
(Leonard:)Hey, guys, can I just say something?
(Leonard:)How about we take a moment
to think about where we are?
I mean, this is literally
the top of the world.
(Leonard:)Only a handful of people
in all of human history...
(Leonard:)...will ever see
what we are going to see.
- He's right.
- Yeah, wow.
(Sheldon:)It is remarkable.
(Raj:)So who's up for a movie?